<changelog>
	<changes>
		<version>0.3-4</version>
		<change>Fix crash due to city not selected for weather data</change>
		<change>Fix crash when page of widget gets removed</change>
		<change>Update UI to truncate names inside of using smaller fonts</change>
		<change>Update weather image padding to be consistent</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.3-3</version>
		<change>Add modern weather widget</change>
		<change>Fix recording module causing a crash on removal</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.3-2</version>
		<change>Add Control Center Module widgets for iOS 13</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.3-1</version>
		<change>Fix today widget sizing issue caused by incompatibility with other tweaks</change>
		<change>Fix potential crash due to race condition between page removal and widget updates</change>
		<change>Improve loading of previews used in album picker of Photos widget</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.3</version>
		<change>Photos Widget rewrite to support album and image picking with iOS 10+ support</change>
		<change>Allow widget addition on empty pages that aren't going to be removed at the end of wiggle mode</change>
		<change>Fix potential crash when dragging widget while page swiped off screen (for reuse)</change>
		<change>Make modern widgets less rounder by default (applies to Battery Widget)</change>
		<change>Developers can now specify custom starting size instead of using the minimum size</change>
		<change>Fix today widget potentially causing crashes due to double free</change>
		<change>Fix today widget causing crashes on iOS 10</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.2-1</version>
		<change>Fix crash when swiping between pages with today widgets</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.2</version>
		<change>Add RTL language support</change>
		<change>Improve placement of accessory buttons when widget is small</change>
		<change>Fix today widget recognizing touches when scrolling between pages</change>
		<change>Add modern battery widget</change>
		<change>make it easier to create custom modern widget view controllers for developers</change>
		<change>Fix insufficient space widgets filtering to not include widgets whose instance limit has been reached</change>
		<change>Make it easier for developers to set the corner radius of custom widgets</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.1-1</version>
		<change>Fix widgets being lost on respring due to reduced motion being enabled or when another tweak disables fly in animation</change>
		<change>Improve UI of widget selection to make it easier to understand when widgets are disabled</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.1</version>
		<change>Redesigned to provide custom widget shapes instead of being restricted to rows</change>
		<change>Add ability to have unique preferences per widget and display them right along the widget</change>
		<change>Add iOS 13 and arm64e compatibility</change>
		<change>Improve compatibility with iPad</change>
		<change>Improve today widget loading</change>
		<change>Add preferences for Clock and Today Widgets</change>
		<change>Add Photo Widget for iOS 13, thanks to Tr1fecta</change>
		<change>Improve API and provide docs for developers to implement their own custom widgets</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.0.1-6</version>
		<change>Improved zoom to center animation for widgets</change>
		<change>Force reconnect today widgets after 12 hours</change>
		<change>Improve today widget loadign after respring for iOS 11+</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.0.1-5</version>
		<change>Rewrote today widget from scratch to get better compatibility with iOS 11+</change>
		<change>Improve compatibility with JellyFish (not completely compatible just yet)</change>
		<change>Fix icon moving issues with tweaks that modify the number of rows on home screen</change>
		<change>Display HSWidgets alphabetically in the Add new widget view</change>
		<change>Fix widgets expansion/shrink causing size issues with multiple widgets on the same page</change>
		<change>Add more layout configuration options (view Layout Configuration link for more information)</change>
		<change>Added A12 device (arm64e) compatibility</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.0.1-4</version>
		<change>Rewrote clock widget from scratch to get better compatibility with iOS 11+</change>
		<change>Fix widgets not being saved correctly when whole pages are removed/shifted</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.0.1-3</version>
		<change>Fix crashes on some devices</change>
		<change>Improve widget loading</change>
		<change>Added option to expand/shrink clock widget</change>
		<change>Added material view background to today widgets for iOS 11+</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.0.1-2</version>
		<change>Fix "X" not showing when going into wiggle mode.</change>
		<change>Fix widget doesn't stop wiggling when leaving wiggle mode.</change>
		<change>Fix tapping "+" not doing anythign by adding IconSupport compatibility.</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.0.1-1</version>
		<change>Fix crashes for iOS 12 due to method name change.</change>
		<change>Fix crashes for iOS 11+ due to variable being removed.</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.0.1</version>
		<change>Initial Release</change>
	</changes>
</changelog>
